<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PloiestiTourGuide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_title">Title</string>
    <string name="text_description">Description</string>
    <string name="text_address">Address</string>
    <string name="image_content_description">attraction_image</string>
    <string name="afi_palace_mall">Afi Palace Mall</string>
    <string name="afi_palace_description"><![CDATA[AFI Palace Ploiesti is a shopping center developed by AFI Europe, one of the leading European investors. Among the retail stores, we include Kendra, Koton, H & M, Intersport, Jolidon, Reserved, Musette, TimeOut, Collins, Nike, Aldo, Otter, Cora and Noriel.]]></string>
    <string name="afi_palace_address">Address: Calomfirescu Street 2</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_center_mall">Ploiesti Shopping Center</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_center_description">This is the ideal place to buy perfect gifts for loved ones; both beautifully and elegantly, this mall offers a wide range of clothing accessories designed to meet the needs of all customers. Simple and yet tasteful, this shopping mall comes to meet you, giving you the opportunity to spend your leisure time and the purchase of products to suit your personal needs.</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_center_address">Address: Victoriei Market 1</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_city_mall">Ploiesti Shopping City</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_city_description">Here you will find over 100 fashion, cosmetics, decorations, jewelery, gifts, electronics and home appliances, restaurants, cafes and useful services such as pharmacy, banking, dry cleaning.</string>
    <string name="ploiesti_shopping_city_address">Address: DN1, Blejoi</string>
    <string name="west_mall">West Mall</string>
    <string name="west_mall_description">Once it arrives at WEST MALL, our client will benefit from a vibrant atmosphere that takes place on the 4 levels of the mall (semi-basement + 3 levels) in the most urban way, in the true sense of the word, where leisure on the terraces , at cafes or fast food will be more recreational with shopping and close service. This is one stop shop, a stop that\'s worth doing.</string>
    <string name="west_mall_address">Address: Vestului Street 1A</string>
    <string name="winmarkt_mall">Winmarkt Ploiesti</string>
    <string name="winmarkt_description">Winmarkt is one of the most extensive network of shopping centers in Romania. The Winmarkt portfolio consists of 15 shopping centers, located in central locations in 13 cities, including 12 county seat, and an office building in Ploiesti.</string>
    <string name="winmarkt_address">Address: Repulicii Boulevard 17-25</string>
    <string name="clock_museum">Clock Museum</string>
    <string name="clock_museum_description">The museum shows a chronological collection of important timepieces: sundials, sand clocks, table clocks, mantle clocks, travel clocks and pocket watches.</string>
    <string name="clock_museum_address">Address: Nicolae Simache Street 1</string>
    <string name="history_acrcheology_museum">History and Archeology Museum</string>
    <string name="history_archeology_museum_description">The building sheltering the museum of the history of Prahova was built in the neoclassical style according to the plans of architect Al. Orăscu</string>
    <string name="history_archeology_museum_address">Address: Toma Caragiu Street 10</string>
    <string name="i_l_caragiale_museum">Ion Luca Caragiale Museum</string>
    <string name="i_l_caragiale_description">This is the museum of one of our greatest writers. It\'s worth visiting not only for the books and the comprehensive collection of items that belonged to him, but also for the nice and professional staff who will answer all your questions.</string>
    <string name="i_l_caragiale_address">Address: Kutuzov Street 1</string>
    <string name="natural_science_museum">Natural Science Museum</string>
    <string name="natural_science_museum_description">The \"Museum of Man\" brings together the most important aspects of human biology: anthropogenesis-anthropology, human races and subraces of Romanian population, anatomy and physiology, genetics, ecology, demography, nature conservation, anthropogenic ecosystems in Romania.</string>
    <string name="natural_science_museum_address">Address: Erou Calin Catalin Street 1</string>
    <string name="national_oil_museum">National Oil Museum</string>
    <string name="national_oil_museum_description">Inaugurated on October 8, 1961 as a result of the centenary celebration of the Romanian oil industry in 1957, is the only museum of its kind in Romania and is hosted by a beautiful building that allowed the arrangement of some rooms and with a courtyard that has been converted into an outdoors exhibition.</string>
    <string name="national_oil_museum_address">Address: Doctor Dumitru Bagdazar Street 8</string>
    <string name="giulia_restaurant">Giulia Restaurant</string>
    <string name="giulia_rest_description">We organize live music events alongside the Vatra band that will have you up till the morning. We make home deliveries of pizzas and other special dishes. We offer catering services for your event wherever it is.</string>
    <string name="giulia_rest_address">Address: Enăchiță Văcărescu Street 12</string>
    <string name="terraverde">TerraVerde</string>
    <string name="terraverde_description">If you have not been to Terraverde yet, we would expect you to come in, choose, taste, tell us what you like but what not. That\'s because for us the CLIENT is the most important referee of this wonderful activity: KITCHEN.</string>
    <string name="terraverde_address">Address: Basarabilor Street 9</string>
    <string name="nabucco">Nabucco</string>
    <string name="nabucco_description">Access is extremely easy and the location has guarded parking spaces. All three sections of the Nabucco restaurant, the event venues and the pub, have separate access, with the events being able to run differently.</string>
    <string name="nabucco_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 307</string>
    <string name="antique_rest">Antique Restaurant</string>
    <string name="antique_rest_description">Antique Restaurant is not just the place to eat, but a destination itself, a special place for different occasions: elegant for a business lunch, warm and welcoming for a meeting between friends.</string>
    <string name="antique_rest_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 295</string>
    <string name="trattoria_prestij">Trattoria Prestij</string>
    <string name="trattoria_prestij_description">Quality services, carefully chosen foods and well-trained staff are our business card. Our locations are in the top of Ploiesti and occasional visitors from other countries.</string>
    <string name="trattoria_prestij_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 219</string>
    <string name="yarus_restaurant">Yarus Restaurant</string>
    <string name="yarus_rest_description">Yarus restaurant with a capacity of 70 people is the perfect choice for organizing various events, receptions, banquets, anniversaries or cocktails.</string>
    <string name="yarus_rest_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 228</string>
    <string name="class_hotel">Class Hotel</string>
    <string name="class_hotel_description">Hotel Class Ploieşti is offering 19 tastefully furnished rooms to those seeking accommodation in Ploieşti. The hotel also welcomes your pet for the stay.</string>
    <string name="class_hotel_address">Address: Maramures Street 6</string>
    <string name="forum_hotel">Forum Hotel</string>
    <string name="forum_hotel_description">Unpretentious rooms and suites come with free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs, minibars and desks. Room service is available. There\'s an unfussy international restaurant, as well as a bar and a garden.</string>
    <string name="forum_hotel_address">Address: Gheorghe Doja Street 215 A</string>
    <string name="mario_hotel">Mario Hotel</string>
    <string name="mario_hotel_description">Cozy rooms with baroque-style wood furnishings and colorful accents provide complimentary Wi-Fi and cable TV, in addition to minibars. Room service is on offer.</string>
    <string name="mario_hotel_address">Address: Sondelor Street 74</string>
    <string name="nord_hotel">Nord Hotel</string>
    <string name="nord_hotel_description">All rooms are fitted with a cable TV, a refrigerator and a private bathroom with a bathtub or a shower, a hairdryer and free toiletries. Some rooms are air-conditioned. WiFi access is available in all public areas.</string>
    <string name="nord_hotel_address">Address: Vestului Street 31</string>
    <string name="acapulco_hotel">Acapulco Hotel</string>
    <string name="acapulco_hotel_description">Classified in the 3 star category, Acapulco Hotel offers accommodation in 15 double rooms and 2 deluxe suites, endowed with ultramodern. The rooms are equipped with modern and spacious bathroom, air conditioning, central heating, TV, mini-bar, telephone, safe, hair dryer, fax in the room, jacuzzi and balcony. Wi-Fi access is available free of charge in the entire location.</string>
    <string name="acapulco_hotel_address">Address: George Coșbuc Street 32</string>
    <string name="best_hotel">Best Hotel</string>
    <string name="best_hotel_description">The warmly decorated rooms feature walnut furnishings, flat-screen TVs, free Wi-Fi and minibars. Room service is available. Amenities include an airy restaurant, a stylish bar and a relaxed terrace with shaded seating. Parking is offered.</string>
    <string name="best_hotel_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 154</string>
    <string name="central_hotel">Central Hotel</string>
    <string name="central_hotel_description">The straightforward rooms offer free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minibars. Upgraded rooms and suites add separate living areas, and/or tea and coffeemakers. Apartments have kitchenettes. Room service is available.</string>
    <string name="central_hotel_address">Address: Republicii Boulevard 1</string>
    <string name="hotel_tab">Hotels</string>
    <string name="food_tab">Food</string>
    <string name="museums_tab">Museums</string>
    <string name="malls_tab">Malls</string>
</resources>
